

Kazeem Amuzat

Front-End Developer

- amuzatk@gmail.com → +234 (0) 7036608365
- Quarters Extension, Jemilu Lion Street, Kuje, FCT, Abuja, Nigeria., +234 903101

Education

B.Tech (Hons.) Mathematics "4.03/5.0"

Jan 2010 - Mar 2016

Ondo State University of Science and Technology, Okitipupa

Mathematics

JavaScript Maters Course

Dec 2020 - Dec 2021

OGTECH NETWORKS LTD, FCT., Abuja

JavaScript

REACTJS

Dec 2021 - May 2022

UDEMY, Online

JavaSript Library for bulding user interfaces

Employment

Front-End Developer

Jul 2020 - Present

K-Devs System Solutions

Software Developer Intern

Jul 2010 - Dec 2020

K-Devs System Solutions, Lagos

HR Executive

Jan 2018 - Oct 2019

Intertech Systems Ltd, Lagos

Profile

I am a FrontEnd Engineer with experience in JavaScript and ReactJs Technologies, I have ditched out application development using the aforementioned stacks with experience in project management (PM). I am currently working at K-Devs System Solutions.

Courses

React - The Complete Guide (inclusive of Hooks, React Router and Redux)

May 2022

React Js methodologies as JavaScript library for user interfaces.

JavaScript

Dec 2021

JavaScript Methodologies.

Personal details

Date of birth July 30th, 1988

Place of birth

lwo

Driver's license

GGE61612AA11

Gender

Male

Nationality

Nigerian

Website

my-news-appbeta.vercel.app

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/kazmatics

Skills

Time management
Organizational skills
Communication skills
Teamwork Conceptual skills
Creative thinking Decision
making Problem solving
Leadership

Languages

English Language and Yoruba Language

Hobbies

Reading, Traveling,
 Computer Simulation
 Games

Internships

Software Developer Intern

Jul 2020 - Dec 2020

K-Devs System Solutions, Lagos

I contributed in coding new mid-features and app testing for eduTech application which contributes positively in achieving the business goal.

Certificates

React JS May 2022

React JS methodologies.

JavaScript Dec 2021

JavaScript Methodologies.

Professional Diploma in Project Aug 2020

Management & Leadership Training -

SHAW ACADEMY

Professional Diploma in Project Management & Leadership Training – SHAW ACADEMY

Workforce Collaboration and Oct 2020

Development

Workforce Collaboration and Development - YALI NETWORK

Advanced Strategic Human Resources Jun 2018

Management

Advanced Strategic Human Resources Management – CLARIONTTECH SERVICES

Project Management Proficiency (PMP) Jul 2017

Project Management Proficiency (PMP) – PALMSLAND CONSULT, NIGERIA

Projects

Among several others, I built a news app that dives into the concept of API and associated endpoints consumptions. It centers, majorly, around admin usability while testing the dexterity of the developer in resolving issues programmatically and the ability to execute route implementations.

https://github.com/amuzatk/My-news-app

References

References available upon request.

Qualities

Creative, energetic, resourceful and productive professional with strong ability to recognize needs, opportunities and possibilities and to take quick and necessary steps when required.